過時
Obsolete.
在慾望無限的時代 根本無關緊要
Irrelevant in an age when desire has become amplified.
而慾望 可以用電填滿
But where lust can be sated electronically.
我們需要的 不僅僅是木盒子
We need something more than just a wooden box.
而是一個裝置
There is a mechanism.
房屋就緒 我們可以入駐
The house is ready. We can adapt.
技術或許進步 但罪惡仍沒有改變
Technology may have advanced, but sin remains unchanged.
純粹 貪婪
Pure. Greed.
慾望 謊言 背叛
Lust. Lies. Betrayal.
新千年 向前猛衝
This new millennium hurtles forward.
信心已失
Faith is lost.
人類已經成為沒有道德的真空
Mankind have become a vacuum without morality.
眾多靈魂尋求更新 更黑暗的體驗
So many souls seeking new and darker experiences.
退化復退化 罪孽復罪孽
Degradation upon degradation, sin after sin.
我們首先要尋找的 便是這種靈魂
So then those are the souls we shall seek out first.
沃特金斯先生 我們知道 我們理解
"Mr. Watkins, we know, we understand,
我們可以幫忙 但你一定要來
"and we can help, but you must come.
在為時已晚之前 來吧
"Come now before it's too late.
來魯道維科55號
"Come to 55 Ludovico Place.
獨自一人 現在
"Alone. Now.
一個有同情心的朋友
A sympathetic friend."
更多R級請收藏永久域名 ykb6.com
沃特金斯先生
Ah, Mr. Watkins.
你能來真是太好了
So good of you to come.
有好東西給你看
We have such sights to show you.
請進屋
Please, step inside.
沃特金斯先生
Mr. Watkins.
這他媽的是怎麼回事
What the fuck is going on?
你他媽是什麼東西
What the fuck are you?
你對我做了什麼
What are you doing to me?
混蛋 真能問問題
Asshole! All valid questions.
這他媽的是怎麼回事
What the fuck is going on?
拜託 沃特金斯先生
Mr. Watkins, please.
請審時度勢
Please assess your situation.
看看處境
Look at your environment.
現在 你只是俘虜
For now, you are merely captive.
坐著 被綁在椅子上
Sitting, tied to a chair.
如果我們要你死 你早死了
If we wanted you killed, then you would be.
我們只是邀請你來談談
We have simply invited you here to talk.
聽你的想法和願望
To hear your thoughts and desires.
如果足夠有趣和啟發
Furthermore, if they're as interesting and illuminating
正如我所相信的那樣 你的獎賞將超出你的信仰
as I believe them to be, then your reward will be beyond your belief.
獎賞
A reward?
為你特別的品味和慾望 量身定做的獎賞
A reward tailored for a man of your particular tastes and desires.
你知道我嗎
You know about me?
你知道我做過的事嗎
You know the things I've done?
這是你的簡歷 引導我們找到你 反過來也一樣
It is that resume of yours that led us to you and in turn you to us.
你是誰
Who are you?
稍微有點啟發
Yes. Perhaps a little illumination.
請勿過於驚慌
Please, try not to be too alarmed.
天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ!
天個鬼
Heavens, no!
同一個城市 完全不同的郵政編碼
Same city. Completely different zip code.
這是怎麼回事 我在哪裡
What is going on here? What... where am I?
必須開始面試了
Mr. Watkins, we really must begin your interview.
很多人等著見你 我們單刀直入吧
So many people for you to see, so let's just dive in, shall we?
2001年8月18日 你引誘小柯特·裡特森 到你的車上
August 18, 2001, you lured little Courtney Rettison to your car.
為什麼
Why?
我 你怎麼知道的 拜託
I... I... how do you know? - Please.
節省時間
Let's save ourselves the time
避免痛苦 誠實回答問題
and you the considerable pain by answering the questions honestly.
顯然此間 你世界的規則不再適用
Clearly this is a place where the rules of your world do not apply.
顯然於我而言 痛苦只不過是一種普通的貨幣
And obviously, I'm a man for whom pain is nothing more than a common currency.
這種貨幣 我會花一些在你身上
I will spend some on you...
如果你喜歡
if you like.
我以前在操場上見過她
I'd seen her at the, uh, the playground before.
我情不自禁
I couldn't help myself.
我理解
I understand.
我只是想幫忙
I was just trying to help.
繼續
Yes, yes.
她有一頭金髮
She had blonde hair.
長髮 馬尾辮
Long, and... it was in a ponytail.
我從未見過這麼多的血 來自這麼小的生物
I've never seen so much blood from a little creature.
勤勞的蜜蜂 沃特金斯先生
My, my. Quite the busy bee we've been, Mr. Watkins.
那我的獎賞呢
What about my reward?
首先 你將與估價師會面
First of all, you will meet with the assessor.
他會審閱記錄 把他的發現傳給陪審團
He will look over your pages, pass on his findings to the jury,
之後再說
and we'll go from there.
估價師很快就來
The assessor will be with you shortly.
孩子們的眼淚
Tears... of children.
幹嘛
What?
你活該  你這個變態
Serves you right, you sick fuck!
女士們 你們的判決
Ladies, your verdict.
有罪
Guilty.
陪審團已商議 並已作出有罪判決
The jury have deliberated, and a guilty verdict has been given.
什麼
What?
你會被帶去清洗 然後再交給外科師
You'll be taken from here to be cleaned and then to the Surgeon.
但我的獎賞呢
But what about my reward?
你註釋說你明白了
Your note said you understood.
說你是朋友
It said you were a friend.
我明白 這是你的獎賞
I do understand. This is your reward.
這就是你應得的 我的朋友
This is what you're deserving of, my friend.
求你
Please!
我會改善的
I'll be better! I'll be good!
是誰 誰
What? Who is it? Who is it?
誰
Who is it?
救救我 請救我
Help me. Please help me, please.
不 求你們
No. Please!
救命 他媽的對我幹嘛 住手
Help! What the fuck are you doing to me? Stop!
你的內心一定也很乾淨
You must be clean on the inside, too.
救命
Help!
更多R級請收藏永久域名 ykb6.com
優步貴賓車 優你妹
Uber Black, my ass!
一坨屎
It's just this piece of shit!
搞什麼鬼
What the hell?
喬希
Josh?
你又在我公寓裡了
You in my apartment again?
我叫你把鑰匙還給我的
I told you that you need to give me my key back.
午夜勝利之歌收場了
Okay. This late-night bootie call shit is over!
雖然我可能匆匆...
Although I could probably go for a quickie...
為了過去的時光
for old times' sake.
喬希
Josh.[FK SUB]
我很快就干了喔
Okay. I'm drying up real fast here.
這個黑暗中的古怪 只會閃現
This weirdo-in-the-dark thing is only a turn-on
就幾分鐘
for like a few minutes.
我的狗呢
And... and where's my dog?
寶貝
Baby?
他媽的
Fuck this!
媽蛋 你把燈怎麼了
Seriously? What the fuck have you done with the lights?
你想要什麼
What do you want?
讓你吸取教訓
To make a lesson out of you.
你氣色極差
You look like shit.
你昨晚做了什麼
What'd you do last night?
精彩嗎
Wonderful. Yeah.
昨晚我過得很愉快 謝謝你問我
I had a great time last night. Thank you for asking.
過兩個街區 泰勒路左轉
You can take a left two blocks up the way on Taylor.
受害者克裡斯特·蘭寧 21歲 今天下午 大樓零時工發現的她
Victim is one Crystal Lanning, 21 years old. Building super found her this afternoon.
我曾泡過一個叫克裡斯特的妞
I went out with a girl called Crystal.
會說話了
It speaks!
什麼故事  - 就像雙城記
What was that like? - Like A Tale of Two Cities.
什麼 - 查爾斯·狄更斯
A what? - Charles Dickens.
對
Right.
就像路人皆知一樣
Like anyone reads that shit anymore.
舉世名著啊
It's the most popular fictional book on the planet.
為什麼這個克裡斯特女郎喜歡這本書
So why is this Crystal chick like the book?
讀它
Read it.
我們到了
We're here.
好
Good.
愛慕這小傢伙
Worship this little guy.
這個地方被清理了 被鎖上了
The place has been cleared, locked down.
所有人待命 直到我們檢查完畢 以防是他
Everyone's been told to hold back until we make our pass in case it's him.
我愛慕這小傢伙
I worship this little guy.
我愛慕這個小  - 很好
I worship this little... - Nice.
我愛慕這小傢伙
I worship this little guy.
是他
It's him.
肯定是他
It's definitely him.
你覺得呢
You think?
這對戒律師來說 是不是太基本了
Doesn't this seem a bit basic for the Preceptor?
你他媽的是誰
Who the fuck are you?
你晚上在案發現場 鬼鬼祟祟的幹什麼
What are you doing creeping around a murder scene at nighttime?
你想死嗎
You want to end up dead?
卡特和卡特偵探
Detectives Carter and Carter.
雙拼兄弟 同姓之人
Brothers in arms... literally.
我是埃傑頓偵探
Detective Egerton.
我已經被分配到這個案子 與你們一起
I've been assigned to this case with you.
你盯著她 - 我來
You got her? - I got her.
克莉絲汀·埃傑頓探長
Detective Christine Egerton.
你介意嗎
Do you mind?
你為什麼來這裡
Why are you here?
哪個認為我們需要幫助的
Who thinks we need help with this?
就像我說的 這對戒律師來說 是不是太基本了
Like I was saying, isn't this just a bit basic for the Preceptor?
我是說 我印象裡
I mean, I was under the impression
他喜歡震驚 驚恐 說教
that he liked to shock, appall, teach.
那呢
And that?
"我是嫉妒之神 對我不可有二心"
"I am a jealous God. Thou shalt have no others unto me"?
餘下的戒律之一 也是他慣用伎倆
It's one of the remaining commandments, and it's part of his MO.
我認為這只是個噱頭
I think that it's just a stunt.
那是什麼 - 上帝
What was that? - Jesus Christ!
那是什麼鬼東西
What the fuck is that?
有人看過錄像裡的狗了嗎
Has anyone seen the dog in the video?
干
Fuck!
沒事了
It's okay.
寶貝
Baby.
那狗是她的寶貝
The dog was her baby.
他把狗放進她的子宮裡
So he put it into her womb.
我得上報局裡了
I'll call it in.
艾莉森的生日 媽的
Alison's birthday. Shit!
不錯
Nice.
1940年代的偵探所
It's uh, very 1940s detective agency.
還是抽雪茄 蘇格蘭威士忌當早飯嗎
Do we still smoke stogies and have scotch for breakfast?
目前這件案子極其黑暗
What we're investigating is very dark.
螢光燈讓我偏頭痛
Fluorescents give me a migraine.
我的到來 你們呆了吧
Look, I know that me coming here must be a bit of a shock.
更多R級請收藏永久域名 ykb6.com
偵探隊伍應親密無間 但我很懂行
Detective teams are tight-knit at the best of times, but I do know this job.
所以 允許的話 我幫得上忙
So, I can help if you let me.
我得走了
I've gotta go.
我妻子生日 我遲到了
It's my wife's birthday and I'm late.
我們明天繼續
We'll do this tomorrow.
9點
9 a.m.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
他有個人恩怨
He takes it personal.
他不該那麼做的 我是被指派的
Well, he shouldn't. I was assigned.
不是針對你
Not you.
是案子
The killings.
這玩意呆在這裡活不了
That won't last in here.
塑料的
Plastic.
氣候再惡劣 也一樣茁壯
Thrives in all climates.
祝我生日快樂
Happy birthday to me.
我來弄吧
I'll take care of that.
我根本不喜歡康乃馨
I don't even like carnations.
我要去睡覺了
I'm going to bed.
蘭尼之前的戒律是
The previous commandment prior to Lanning was
"你不應說謊 " 這家是天主教家庭
"Thou shall not lie." This is a Catholic family.
傑西卡和史蒂文都是律師
Jessica and Steven were both lawyers.
戒律師用電動火雞刀割掉了兩人的舌頭
The Preceptor cut out both of their tongues with an electric turkey knife.
讓他們的兒子邁克爾 目睹流血
Let them bleed out in front of their own son, Michael.
他把舌頭怎麼了
What did he do with the tongues?
放進攪拌機裡 強迫餵給兒子 用漂白劑處理過
He put them in a blender and force-fed them to the son, laced with bleach, of course.
甜甜圈麼
Donut?
他為什麼要把舌頭餵給兒子
Now why would he feed the tongues to the son?
他說夫婦倆向每個人灌輸謊言 所以他把謊言餵給了他們兒子
He said they were feeding lies to everyone, so he fed their lies to their son.
你們怎麼知道這些的
How do you guys know all this?
他是書信家 顯然 我們搞到了副本
He's quite the letter writer. We have copies obviously.
我給你拿一些 - 說到這個...
I'll get you some. - Speaking of which...
這是今早從法醫辦公室傳來的
this came from the ME's office this morning.
從蘭尼的腹部拿出來的
Got it out of Lanning's abdomen.
"本殺戮的諷刺在於 當人們看到我的所為"
"The irony of this killing is that when people see what I've done,
"他們的反應會是:可憐的狗"
"their reaction will be, 'Oh, poor dog, '
"居然被這麼埋了"
"with no consideration for the vacuous vessel in which I chose to store it."
很好 - 證據全在字裡行間了嗎
Nice. - Forensics has been over the letters?
警察和中情局 都沒結果嗎
Local and Langley. Came out with nothing.
信是用舊手動打字機打的字 普通墨水
Letter was typed on an old manual typewriter. Common ink.
沒有指紋 油 殘渣 膠水 微粒 什麼都沒有
No prints, oils, residue, glue, particulates. Nothin'.
"戒律師"是共濟會的術語 所在地檢查過了嗎
The name Preceptor. That's a Masonic term. Has that avenue been checked out?
雖然由共濟會使用 但實際歷史更久遠
It's used by Freemasons, but it's older than that.
戒律是教師用於維護法律或傳統的
A precept is a teacher responsible to uphold law or tradition.
本案中 有十誡
In this case, the Ten Commandments.
我可以嗎 - 稍等
Shall I? - Just one second.
現在總計有多少受害者
How many victims are we talking about in total now?
14名
Fourteen.
還剩兩誡 - "你不應偷竊"
Two commandments left. - "Thou shall not steal."
"你不應垂涎 "
"Thou shall not covet."
請問你的背景 你何必要辦這案子
Can I ask you what exactly is your background? Why are you on this case?
當然 你可以問我任何事
Of course. You can ask me anything.
我們可以按順序 從上到下進行審理嗎
Can we go through the cases in order, top to bottom?
成為偵探前 必須幹上兩年取證工作
You worked forensics two years before you became a detective.
接手另一名偵探的工作 需要重新擼一遍嗎
Did it take a lot of detective work to find out about another detective?
是不是高層認為我們在搗糨糊
Someone higher up think we're screwin' this up?
高層希望這傢伙被抓住 就這麼簡單
Someone higher up wants this guy caught, and it's as simple as that.
那好 我們來吧
Okay. Let's do this.
好的
Okay.
某種意義上 我們都是...由他言辭的力量
At a point, we're all... by the word of his power,
當他淨化...
when he has made purification his...
...以陛下之右手
at the right hand of His Majesty on high.
因為你肉體的軟弱 我用人話來表達
I am speaking in human terms because of the weakness of your flesh,
因為正如你所奉獻的...
for just as you presented...
那些不純的雜質和目無法紀
...blazed with the impurities and true lawlessness
導致進一步的無法無天
resulting in further lawlessness,
所以現在奉上你的成員 為了正義而閃耀
so now present your members as blazed to righteousness,
才能修得正果
resulting in sanctification.
你沒事吧
You all right?
讓她去
Let her go.
你覺得他們是誰
Who do you think they are?
警察要挨家挨戶檢查監控
Uniforms are going door to door to check the CCTVs.
我操
Fuck me!
以眼還眼 以牙還牙
Eye for an eye, tooth for a tooth.
蒂芙尼·納迪庫 年齡12 艾米莉·卡特賴特 13歲
Tiffany Nardico, age 12, Emily Cartwright, 13.
蘇珊·埃裡森 14歲 妮可·潘娜 15歲
Susan Allison, 14, and Nicole Panna, 15.
他們都有案底 但差不多都是小偷小摸
They all have records, but it's just like petty theft.
可以嗎
Okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我剛和霍奇斯通了電話
I just got off the phone with Hodges.
驗屍官
The medical examiner.
頭髮 牙齒和眼睛 與手匹配
Preliminaries for the hair, teeth, and eyes are a match with the hands.
罐子裡的血跡也一樣
Same with the blood in the jar.
所以共計4名受害者
So it's just the four victims.
兇手在手裡注射了環氧樹脂 維持形狀
The killer injected some kind of epoxy into the hands to keep them in position.
還有別的嗎 是
Anything else? - Yes.
指尖沒有凝固
No coagulation in the fingertips.
媽的
Shit!
怎麼
What?
意思是 活著被砍掉的手部
He cut their hands off while they were still alive.
上帝
Jesus!
這些是他們嗎 是
Are those them? - Yeah.
什麼名字  - 妮可·潘娜
What name is that? - Nicole Panna.
你有想法嗎
Hm. Does that mean anything to you?
沒有 為什麼 應該有嗎
No, why? Should it?
卡爾·沃特金斯
Carl Watkins.
誰
Who?
地方罪犯
Local perp.
拍照者 兒童色情小販
Flasher. Kiddie porn peddler.
我們逮了他幾次 但他總是認罪 或用情報交易
We picked him up a couple times, but he always pled out or made a deal informing.
他與此何干
So what does he have to do with this?
這些女孩 都念過切斯·泰拉斯學院
All of these girls went to Chase Terrace Academy.
泰拉斯在被捕幾次後 被提出了限制令
Terrace put a restraining order against him after he was caught a few times
因為在體育課 對著女孩們手淫
loitering and jerking off to the girls in gym class.
真是太誇張了 大衛
That's a real stretch, David.
你猜幾年前 還有誰還去過泰拉斯
Guess who also went to Terrace a few years back?
克裡斯特·蘭尼
Crystal Lanning.
正解
Exactly.
真的嗎
Seriously?
我們有他的最新住址嗎
Do we have a current address on him?
他不在
He's not in.
那個混蛋欠我兩個月的房租
That cocksucker owes me two months' rent.
他已經幾天沒來了 - 你覺得他會躲在裡面嗎
He hasn't been here for a couple of days. - Think he'd be hiding out inside?
如果是 他會在黑暗中凍死的
If he is, he's freezing his ass off in the dark.
我昨天切斷了他的電源
I cut his power yesterday.
不會吧 沒有窗戶
Seriously? No windows?
親愛的 那些傢伙在裡面幹的事 沒有窗戶更好
Honey, with what those boys are doin' in there, no windows ain't a bad thing.
走時把門關上
Shut the door when you leave.
一股怪味
What an incredible smell you've discovered.
不需要太久的
Oh, this shouldn't take long.
這傢伙似乎有助手
This guy seems to have quite the right arm.
似乎不像戒律師
Doesn't really seem like the Preceptor type.
說魔鬼 魔鬼到
Speak of the devil.
像是用舊手動打字機打字的
Looks like it's typed on an old manual typewriter.
送到實驗室去吧
Let's get that back to the lab.
對沃特金斯調用高級技術檢測
Uh-hm. - Put out an ATL on Watkins.
在此期間 我們去找普通嫌疑犯
In the meantime, let's hit the usual suspects.
你和大衛一起去
You go with David.
有發現嗎
Anything?
沒
Nope.
今天沒事了嗎
Done for the day?
是的
Yeah.
回家的路上 我要去一趟沃特金斯的公寓
I'm going to swing by Watkins' apartment on the way home.
怎麼了
What's up?
我有點心煩
Somethin's been buggin' me about it.
代我向那位嘴甜的女房東問好
Give our regards to that sweet-mouthed landlady for me.
我會把你的號碼給她的
I'll give her your number.
謝謝 接通電源
Thanks for turnin' the power on.
更多R級請收藏永久域名 ykb6.com
對不起 肖恩·卡特探長
Excuse me. Detective Sean Carter.
卡特先生
Mr. Carter.
卡特先生 你對我們有興趣
Mr. Carter. You're a man of some interest to us.
你想知道什麼
What do you want to know?
對不起  - 你顯然想問問題
Excuse me? - You obviously have questions.
何以見得
Why would you say that?
因為如果你想讓我死 我早就死了
Because if you wanted me dead, I'd be dead already.
這是真的 還有什麼
That's very true. What else?
我猜 我已經陷入了痛苦而致命的局勢
If I had to guess, I've stumbled into a painful, possibly fatal situation,
你很快就會告訴我接下來的事
the agenda of which you'll soon tell me.
你能說說卡爾·沃特金斯嗎
What can you tell me about Carl Watkins?
顯然是個品味完美的人
A man of impeccable taste, apparently.
能說說戒律師嗎 - 我也想問你同樣的問題
What can you tell me about the Preceptor? - I was about to ask you the same question.
這些是什麼
What are those?
既然你如此優秀 我們別浪費時間於世俗的...
Well, since you've been good enough not to waste our time with the usual drudgery
你是誰 救命之類
of who are you and save me, et cetera,
或有獎賞
perhaps a reward is in order.
天哪 我在哪裡
Dear God! Where am I?
你知道嗎
You wanted to know about these.
它們是你我世界之間的聯繫裝置
They are a linking mechanism between our world and yours.
是對打開者的審判和救贖
They are judgment and redemption to those who open them.
它們代表感覺
They are sensation,
重生 死亡
rebirth... death,
慾望 憎恨
lust... hate.
所有的情感
All manner of emotions.
它們是通向虛妄的管道
They are a conduit to the unimaginable.
藉由木箱嗎
In a wooden box.
打開時 你會驚訝的
You'd be amazed what they can do when opened.
這到底什麼地方
What on earth is this place?
什麼也不是
It isn't.
現在如何
So now what?
過程的開始 一次面試
This is the beginning of a process, an interview.
按序審計
An audit of sorts.
你想要誠實的答案吧
And you want honest answers.
絕對
Absolutely.
那我們就開始吧
So then let's just get on with it.
光陰似箭
Tempus fugit after all.
告訴我 你第一次傷害別人是幾時
Tell me, when was the first time you hurt something?
老實說 卡特先生
Be honest, Mr. Carter.
你越早說真話 越早自由
The sooner you tell the truth, the sooner you will be free.
Four.
我們養了只寵物狗
We had a pet dog.
我打了它
I hit it.
繼續嗎 - 2004年3月31日
Should I go on? - March 31, 2004.
我25歲
I was 25.
子彈擊中了喉嚨
The bullet hit him in the throat.
我看見拳頭大小的物體 被射出頸後
I saw a fist-size chunk blown out the back of his neck.
我站在面前 看著它死去
I stood over him and watched him die.
然後呢
And after that?
兩個孩子
Two kids.
手榴彈
Grenade.
這是我第一次看到肉體被炸成碎片
It was the first time I'd ever seen a body blown to pieces.
皮肉分離
Skin stripped from muscle.
骨肉離析
Flesh stripped from bone.
你是保護祖國的人
You were a man protecting his country.
你被允許執行這些行為
You were permitted to carry out these acts,
但你能感覺到什麼
but what were you permitted to feel?
你有什麼感覺  - 我有什麼感覺
What did you feel? - What did I feel?
我到底有什麼感覺
What the hell was I supposed to feel?
你殺了很多人
You have killed a great many people.
我是在盡責
I was doing my job.
如此你便可免除自己 無辜鮮血的罪惡感了嗎
You will purge from yourself the guilt of shedding innocent blood.
因為你們在耶和華眼中做了正確的事
For you have done what is right in the eyes of the Lord.
只有上帝才能審判我
Only God can judge me!
神必審判義人和惡人
And God will judge both the righteous man and the wicked man.
傳道書3:17
Ecclesiastes 3:17.
申命記21:9
Deuteronomy 21:9.
我想再深入一點
I would like to dig a little deeper.
我有什麼選擇
What choice do I have?
沒有
None.
第二次出征 車隊被擊中 我
On my second tour, the convoy hit, and I...
還有更多
There are still more.
"你正在製造可怕而笨重的鎖鏈 守財奴"
"It is a terrible, ponderous chain you are making, Scrooge."
查爾斯·狄更斯
Charles Dickens.
現在如何
Now what?
接下來 你會遇到估價師
Next, you'll meet the assessor,
好一頓大餐等著他
and my, what a meal he has ahead of him.
你做了什麼
What have you done?
你將被帶去清洗 然後交給外科師
You will be taken to be cleaned and then to the surgeon.
不 不可能
Oh. No, it can't be.
我討厭這個地方
I hate this place.
惡臭 黑暗的洞穴
The stench, the dark hole.
破爛的遊戲和放縱
The seedy games and indulgences
我們安排你上場
we allow you to play as part of the arrangement.
你為什麼來此  - 讓他走
Why are you here? - Let him go.
他與此無關 - 我不明白
He has no business here. - I don't understand.
雖然它落入你的網 但並不為蜘蛛所捕獵
Well, just because it falls into your web does not make it prey for the spider.
捉與放 你明白嗎
Catch and release. Do you understand?
那估價師呢 - 記錄錯誤 字面上的
What about the assessor? - Clerical error, quite literally.
我從未  - 我不在乎
I've never... - I don't care!
陪審團從未裁決無罪 所以你得讓他走 明白嗎
The jury never passed their verdict. You'll let him go, do you understand?
不 - 你知道是誰發號施令嗎
Not really, no. - Well, do you understand who is in charge?
讓他走吧
So let him go.
不要給我回來的理由
Do not give me a reason to come back here.
你裡面也必須洗乾淨
You must be cleaned on the inside too!
不
No!
一瞬間
A moment of your time.
一個候選人
A-a candidate...
我需要你們的協助 指引
I need your assistance with your... your guidance.
什麼
What?
他的回答使估價師窒息
His answers choked the assessor.
迫使了陪審團
Forced the jury in.
那麼...您的感覺是
So... what do you feel?
無辜
Innocent?
他現在在哪裡
Where is he now?
我送他去清洗
I sent him to be cleaned.
他走了
He's gone!
帶走了一個箱子
Escaped with one of the boxes.
記錄
The pages.
拿著
Take.
吃這個是為了提醒我的身體
Eat this in remembrance of my body.
你必須去追他
You must go after him.
把他帶回來 必須深入挖掘
Bring him back. We must dig deeper.
我們必須弄清你的感受 等你釋懷
We must find out what you feel once you've released.
沒必要去追他
There's no need to go after him.
他會回來的
He'll be back.
現在是兩點半
It's 2:30 in the morning.
你有手電筒嗎
You... you got your flashlight?
有啊 怎麼了 - 我開車
Yeah, why? - I'll drive.
怎麼了
Why? What's up?
這是怎麼回事
What's going on?
需要上報嗎
You want to call this in?
我們在這裡做什麼
What are we doing here?
我們在這幹嘛
What the fuck are we doing here?
那麼
So?
拜託 夥計
Come on, man!
不錯的地方
Nice. Nice place.
又有委託嗎
Put an offer in yet?
還是你失業了 - 他媽的
Or are you in escrow? - Fuck.
到底怎麼回事
What is going on?
你把我累死累活半夜拖過來 卻沒有解釋
You drag my ass out here in the middle of the fucking night with no explanation?
你也不跟我說話 夥計
You barely talk to me anymore, man.
艾莉森很擔心你
Alison is worried about you.
你知道的
Oh, you'd know that.
夥計 我們都很擔心你 肖恩
Man, we're all worried about you, Sean.
我開車送你回你的車
I'll drive you back to your car.
它們是通向虛妄的管道
They are a conduit to the unimaginable.
感覺 重生 死亡 慾望 憎恨
Sensation, rebirth, death, lust, hate.
這只是個夢
It's just a dream.
只是個夢 你沒事的
Just a dream. You're okay.
沒事了 過來 過來
It's okay. Come here. Come here.
沒事了
It's okay.
我不知道怎麼回事
I don't know what's goin' on anymore.
這個案子 正在毀了你
This case... it's destroying you.
肖恩
Sean!
怎麼了
What?
怎麼回事 你在做什麼
What is going on? What are you doing?
搞什麼
What...
對打開者的審判和救贖
Judgment and redemption to those who open the box.
謝謝
Thank you.
杏仁奶
Almond milk.
謝謝
Thanks.
你在想什麼
So what's on your mind?
你哥哥嗎
Your brother?
只是好奇
Just curious.
你呆了幾天 都看到了什麼
You been here for a couple of days, what do you see?
我看到兩個人陷入了極度黑暗的案子
I see two people mired in a pretty dark case.
其中一個可能深陷其中
One of whom is probably internalizing a little bit too much of it.
老實說 我還和從前一樣
Honestly, I don't know that I would be any different.
他有問題
Yeah, he's not running right.
你和別人談過了嗎 - 非正式的 但我和他妻子談過了
Did you talk to somebody about that? - Not official, but I do talk to his wife.
艾莉森 - 你怎麼知道的
Alison. - Yeah. How did you know that?
他復員時 有沒有被診斷為創傷後應激障礙
Did he ever suffer from any PTSD when he came back?
至少我不知道 但他從未真正提起戰場
Not that I know of, but he's never really talked about what went on over there.
酗酒 吸毒呢
Drinking, drugs?
沒有嗎
None of that?
他喝過一陣子 但現在已經清醒了
He drank for a little while, but he is sober now.
只是最近他很疏遠
Just lately he's been distant.
我想也許開始對他有影響了
I think maybe it's starting to have an effect on him.
我
I...
什麼
What?
我被分配到這個案子有兩個原因
Look, I was assigned to this case for two reasons:
其中之一是加快捕捉戒律師
One of them is to expedite the catching of the Preceptor
另一個原因 是因為有人擔心肖恩的行為
and the other is because there are some concerns about Sean's behavior.
我的首要任務是幫助你們辦案  同時也要執行評估
So, I am here first and foremost to help you with the case but also to evaluate.
我們為這案子拼了老命
We've been working our ass off on this case.
與此無關
And it's not about that!
問題在於那個陷得太深的人
This is genuine concern for someone who might be in too deep.
是艾莉森
It's Alison.
你好
Hey, you.
什麼
What?
他是嗎
He is?
別擔心 我會過來接他的
Don't worry about it. I'll come by and pick him up.
你帶莎拉去學校
You take Sara to school.
好
Okay.
他的車壞了 得去接他了
His car broke down. Have to go pick him up.
為什麼不是他打電話給你
He didn't call you?
我得走了
I gotta go.
肖恩
Sean!
我去洗個澡
I'll, uh, I'll go take a shower.
請稍等一下
Ah, wait a second, please.
你得抖擻精神
You got to straighten up.
以防萬一埃傑頓對我們有其他動機
Just in case Egerton has other motivations for being with us.
什麼意思
Meaning what?
想想吧
Think about it.
你忍了多久 又再次喝酒
How long have you been drinking again?
艾莉森和我吵了一架
Alison and I got in a bit of a fight.
我喝了幾杯 就上了頭
I had a few drinks. It caught up with me.
我知道了
I got this.
去收拾乾淨
Go get cleaned up.
肖恩
Sean...
沒有人在審判你
no one is judging you.
就像我對別人說的 只有上帝才能審判我
Like I told somebody else, only God can judge me.
神必審判義人和惡人
God will judge both the righteous man and the wicked man.
雙城記
"這是最美好的時代
"It was the best of times.
"這是最糟糕的時代
"It was the worst of times."
如果我有這樣的關係
If I had a relationship like that...
你好
Hello.
看看這個
Take a look at this.
這是戒律師的第一封信
This is the first letter from the Preceptor.
讀這裡
Read here.
"無需責任 我要帶回全能者的忿怒
"There is no accountability. I will bring back the wrath of the Almighty.
我將是報應的瘟疫
"I will be the plague of retribution.
"這將是黑暗和絕望之冬"
"It will be the season of darkness and winter of despair." And?
我剛在肖恩家發現了這個
And I just found this at Sean's house.
狄更斯 他沒告訴你嗎
Hmmm, Dickens. He didn't tell you about this?
他提到了這本書 但他沒有提到這個
He mentioned the book, but he didn't mention this.
也許他偶然放在一起的 - 那他為什麼沒有提起
Well, maybe he just put it together. - Then why didn't he say anything?
我不知道 你應該問他 他在哪
I don't know. You should ask him. Where is he?
他正在路上 - 我以為他車有麻煩
He's on his way. - I thought he had some kind of car trouble.
他汽車沒有故障 他喝醉了 我得去幫他
He did not have car trouble. He was drunk, and I had to go help him.
你說他很清醒 - 他曾 他現在清醒了
You said he was sober. - He was. He is.
大衛 到底怎麼了 - 我不知道 所以我才來找你
David, what the fuck is going on? - I don't know. That's why I came to you.
我們要和他談談
We're going to have to talk to him.
好
Okay.
跟誰談 -  你 你的臉怎麼了
Talk to who? - You. What happened to your face?
談什麼
About what?
你好
Hello.
是 我是卡特
Yes, this is Carter. Yes. That Carter.
是他幹的
He did.
到底什麼
What exactly?
手機 哪裡
Phone? Where?
我們會去的
We'll be there.
驗屍官
Medical examiner.
找到了克裡斯特·蘭尼的手機
Found Crystal Lanning's cell phone.
楔入她的喉嚨
Wedged down her throat.
你在開玩笑吧 - 他要我們去那兒
You're kidding me. - He wants us there.
好
Okay.
你和我去
You and I go.
大衛留在這裡 核驗證據
David stays here and goes through some of that evidence.
好
Okay.
媽的
Shit!
忘了手機 等我一下
Forgot my phone. Just give me a sec.
忘了手機嗎
Forget your cell phone?
需要你幫我個忙 快去看看周圍
Need you to do me a favor. Take a quick look around.
看有沒有不尋常
See if you find anything unusual.
我不調查我哥 - 這並非請求
I'm not investigating my brother. - I'm not asking you to.
去看看吧 為了他好
Take a look. For his sake.
OK
Okay.
看來現在跑得不錯了
Well, it seems to be running okay now.
什麼
What?
車 大衛說你今早遇到汽車故障
The car. David said you had some car trouble this morning.
婚姻問題
Marriage trouble.
至少你是誠實的
At least you're honest.
我能問你點事嗎 真心的
Can I ask you something? Honestly?
你覺得你太陷入此案嗎
Do you think you're too close to this case?
可能 但這是我的工作
Probably, but it's my work.
但如果它撕裂了你的世界
Yeah, but if it's tearing your world apart.
我能做什麼 只剩下一條戒律了
What can I do? There's only one commandment left.
我得把這一切都做完 對嗎
Got to finish it all the way to the end, right?
明白 令人欽佩 但這並非使命
I get that, and I think it's really admirable, but this is not a tour of duty.
這是給我的
It is for me.
我正在讀戒律師的筆記
I was reading through some of the notes from the Preceptor.
我注意到很多話的轉折 很有詩意
I noticed a lot of the turn of phrase is very poetic.
讀起來有文學味
Almost reads like literature.
大衛提到 你讀了很多書
You know, David mentioned that you read a lot,
所以我想問你 有沒有什麼觸動了你的心弦
so I thought I'd ask if anything struck a chord with you.
沒有
Not really.
狄更斯的雙城記是多線小說
I mean, there are a couple of lines lifted from A Tale of Two Cities by Dickens,
但我於本案沒有別的想法
but nothing else comes to mind.
你在調查中 一點也沒有聯想到嗎
Did you bring that up in the investigation?
似乎不相關
Didn't seem relevant.
畢竟 它是世界名著
After all, it is the most popular book on the planet.
(一切正常)嗯
Yeah.
我想是
I guess it is.
霍奇斯
Hodges.
Hodges. - Hey.
看
See...
你說你找到了一部手機 - 確實 在她喉嚨裡
I thought you said you found a cell phone. - We did. In her throat.
那是在她嘴裡發現的
We found that in her mouth first.
銀的嗎
Silver?
含著銀勺出生的
Born with a silver spoon in her mouth.
起碼死的時候含著銀勺
She certainly died that way.
在她的食道發現的
We found this in her esophagus.
在下面
Way down in there.
真可惜
Damn shame.
她才21
Yeah. She was only 21.
絕對
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
沒有人有 iPhone 7
Nobody has an iPhone 7.
我還用蘋果4
I still got a 4.
謝謝霍奇斯 謝謝你的消息
Thanks, Hodges. Thanks for the information.
還能用呢
It still works.
什麼 - 手機
What? - The phone.
這邊有個孩子有同一型號 所以我們設法充電了
Yeah. One of the kids here has the same model, so we managed to power the thing up.
然後 發現她開啟了GPS定位程序
When we did, it turns out she was using the GPS app.
手機最後位置不是她的公寓吧 - 對  我們查過了
The location on it wasn't her apartment? - No. We checked.
她也沒在公寓裡被殺
She wasn't killed in the apartment either.
他的所為很費時間  搞的一團糟
What he did took time, and uh, would leave quite the mess.
對 尤其是處理狗
Yeah, especially with the dog.
他是把她活人帶走的 預備好 再殺了她
No. He took her somewhere alive, prepped her, killed her.
幸運的是 她的手機和她一起死(沒電)了
Luckily, if you can say that, her phone died with her.
所以 它儲存了她最後的位置
So, it stored her last location.
連環殺手被智能手機抓住了
Serial killer caught by smart phone.
你有地址嗎
Do you have the address?
我以前沒見過你
You know, I haven't seen you around here before.
是的 我剛被指派辦案
Yeah. I was just assigned to the case.
一個人嗎
Single?
你開玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
我要上報
I'll call it in.
是 我是肖恩·卡特探長
Yeah. This is Detective Sean Carter.
我們在嫌疑現場 請求武力支援
We're on the scene of a possibly compromised location. Requesting uniform backup.
地址是  格萊斯頓12437
Address is 12437 Gladstone.
好像是個廢棄倉庫
Looks like a disused warehouse of some kind.
好 收到
Okay. Copy that.
位置絕對能鎖定了
I think this is pretty locked up.
我們得等著
Yeah. Guess we'll be waiting.
我似乎聽到某種爭鬥 是在破壞證據嗎
I don't know. I think I hear a struggle of some kind, destruction of evidence.
我什麼都沒聽到
I don't hear anything.
若你聽到 便不用等搜查令了 你想抓住這傢伙的吧
If you did, we wouldn't have to wait for a warrant. You want to catch this guy, right?
當然了 - 那麼我們便聽到了爭鬥
Of course I do. - Then we hear a struggle.
這邊
Over here.
看看這個
Look at this.
是他
It's him.
我靠
Holy shit!
放下
Drop it!
擦
Fuck!
增援在路上 - 沒有
Backup's on the way. - No, they're not.
已經來了
But someone is.
現在去屋子中間
Now move to the fucking center of the room.
你怎麼知道的
How did you find out?
你告訴我的
You told me.
他說過什麼 "只有上帝能審判我"
What was it he said? "Only God can judge me.
"上帝審判義人"
"God will judge the righteous.
"上帝會審判義人和惡人 '"
"God will judge both the righteous man and the wicked man. '"
"傳道書是希伯來聖經的24本書之一
"Ecclesiastes is one of the 24 books of the Tanakh or Hebrew Bible.
第一本傳道書是拉丁語音譯
"The title Ecclesiastes is a Latin transliteration
原意為希臘語的"教師"
"of the Greek translation originally translated as 'teacher'
或"傳道者"
"or 'preacher'
或"戒律師"
or 'preceptor'."
戒律師
Preceptor.
媽的
Shit!
我失去埃傑頓消息時 我打電話給霍奇斯 獲取地址
When I didn't hear back from Egerton, I called Hodges to get the address.
相當的偵探
Quite the detective.
你為什麼要這麼做
Why are you doing this?
正如我一直告訴你的 你應多讀聖經類
Like I've always told you, you should read more starting with the Bible.
肖恩
Sean?
你不會叫增援抓捕你哥的 除非你確定
You wouldn't call backup on your own brother. Not until you knew for sure.
所以我喊了別人
So, I called someone else.
在這裡
In here.
我盡可能快地趕來了
I came as fast as I could.
媽的
Shit!
肖恩 你在幹什麼
Sean, what are you doing?
肖恩
Sean?
這是什麼 怎麼回事
What is this? What's going on?
進來吧 甜心 靠近我親愛的弟弟旁邊
Come on in, sweetheart. Come stand next to my dear brother.
不 不
No, no.
去站在大衛旁邊
Go stand next to David.
我沒說可以碰她
I didn't say touch her!
我為你們倆安排了這麼多的計劃
I have so much more planned for the two of you.
那個蘭尼婊子的手機把事情搞砸了
That Lanning bitch's cell phone fucked things up!
我不明白
I don't understand.
你不明白
You don't?
環顧四周
Look around.
看看我做了什麼
Look at what I've done.
這是上帝的愛 我們遵守他的誡命
This is the love of God that we keep his commandments,
他的誡命不是累贅
and his commandments are not burdensome.
埃傑頓在哪裡
Where is Egerton?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
肖恩 不不
Sean, no, no.
等等 我們
Wait, wait. We... we...
這個妓女 在網上劈腿
This whore cheated on me with some guy she met online
就在我第一次出征兩周後
two weeks after I left for my first tour.
對不起
I'm sorry.
你不應覬覦別人的妻子
Thou shall not covet another man's wife.
所以我割下他的眼皮 把他活活燒死在自己的車裡
So I cut his eyelids off and burned him alive in his own car.
我對她並不震驚 但我對你期望頗多
I wasn't surprised with her, but I expected more of you.
肖恩 我
Sean, I am...
智能手機癮君子的瘟疫
A plague of smart phone junkies.
我厭惡現代世界
I... loathe the modern world.
我討厭平頭百姓
I loathe the populace.
如果我有辦法 我會把他們都燒成灰燼
If I had the means and ways, I would incinerate them all.
下火雨和硫磺
Rain down fire and sulphur.
現在
Now.
我要你們面對面坐著
I want you to sit down in front of each other.
照做
Just do it!
你打算怎麼做
What are you going to do?
打開
Open that.
什麼
What?
這他媽的是什麼
What the fuck is this?
打開 你倆 現在 一起
Open it. Both of you. Now. Together.
怎麼了 什麼情況
What is this? What's happening?
審判
Judgment!
我知你 最終會找到你的路
I knew you would find your way here eventually.
畢竟
After all...
邪惡尋求邪惡
evil seeks evil.
我就知道有人會來找我的
I knew someone would come for me.
我會節省時間 並與你達成協議
So, I thought I'd save you the time and offer you a deal.
沒有協議
There is no deal to be made.
他們於我
Them for me.
姦淫
Adulterers.
他們打開了盒子
They opened the box.
他們將被相應地處理
And they will be dealt with accordingly.
這是內訌 不可討價還價
It is a separate faction who has want of you, and there is no bargaining to be done.
卡特先生
Ah, Mr. Carter.
很高興再次見到你
So good to see you again.
你還帶了朋友來
And you brought friends.
我帶他們來換我的
I brought them to trade for me.
事情不是這麼辦的
That is not how it works.
我不會再回到那個房間了
I won't go back in that room.
卡特先生 拜託 這玩意現在對你沒用了
Mr. Carter, please. That won't work for you now.
卡特先生
Mr. Carter.
你被陪審團判罰有罪
You have been found guilty by the jury.
你會被帶去清理 再一次
You'll be taken to be cleaned... again.
然後去見外科師 - 不是我
And then to the Surgeon. - Not me!
你的審判記錄如此腐臭
The pages of your audit were so rancid
你有罪的本質
with the essence of your guilt,
甚至令估價師窒息
they made even the Assessor choke.
當外科師和屠夫結束你時
When the Surgeon and the Butcher are finished with you,
你將重生為永恆的痛苦
you will be reborn into an eternity of agony.
這他媽的是怎麼回事
What the fuck is going on?
收聲
Silence!
你們那可憐的通姦罪 臣服吧
Your pitiful adultery is beneath me.
你們比你的兄弟創造的污穢記錄更污穢
Bow your head to the catalog of filth your brother has created.
菜鳥
Amateurs.
但我們會讓他們體驗
But still we will afford them an experience
遠超你名下的限度
beyond the limits in your name.
離他遠一點
Get away from him.
你感覺如何 伊甸園的守門人
How do you feel, Eden's doorman?
那是從前
Once upon a time.
那從前的感覺如何
And then what was it?
看著方舟建造者的亂倫後代 直到現在
Watching over the ark-builder's incestuous offspring until now.
我想把地下室變個樣子
I want to turn this basement into misfits.
他被判有罪
He was found guilty.
放他走
Let him go!
這裡有更大的計劃
There are matters at play here that are part of a bigger plan.
他是其中的一部分
And he is a part of it.
你想讓他留在現世...
You want him now to remain on Earth...
或者更確切地說 他不希望此人呆在另一頭
or rather He wants him out of there.
他希望他的教眾殺雞儆猴 這樣他們就會趨向光明
He wants his flock afraid of the horse so that they look toward the light.
你不像看起來那麼傻
You're not as foolish as you look.
但他所做的事 他所殺的無辜者呢
But what about the things he has done, the innocents he has killed?
可接受的損失
Acceptable losses.
善不能無惡
Good cannot exist without evil.
我們很久以前就發現 為了控制邪惡
And we discovered long ago that in order to control the evil,
我們必須是執行者
we had to be the ones implementing it.
上天注定的罪
Sin ordained by Heaven.
把他送回去
Send him back.
繼續你的工作 戒律師
Continue with your work, Preceptor.
以我們的祝福
With our blessing.
耶和華看見世人的大罪
And the Lord saw that the sin of man was great on the Earth,
他心中所有的思想皆屬邪惡
and that all the thoughts of his heart were evil.
我們的所為
There is process...
皆遵循秩序
order to what we do.
把他送回去
Send him back!
不然呢
Or?
不然代價昂貴
There will be hell to pay.
代...價...昂貴
Hell... to... pay.
別考驗我
Don't test me!
很好
Very well.
現在給我滾出去
Now get me the fuck outta here!
我被原諒了
I've been forgiven.
沒有原諒
Not forgiven.
什麼 - 你是殺人犯
What? - You're a murderer!
變態虐待狂
A twisted sadist.
現在 你的行為對我們有利
For now, your actions work in our favor.
但最終會有你的審判
But there will be judgment for you eventually.
我們會等待的
And, we will be waiting.
操你媽
Fuck you!
現在把他送回去
Now send him back.
樂意之至
With pleasure.
我回來了
I'm back.
"這是我一生中最..."
"Tis a far, far..."
警員倒下 格萊斯頓12437
We have an officer down at 12437 Gladstone.
派救護車
Send assistance.
我是埃傑頓
This is Egerton.
我們有戒律師
We have the Preceptor.
派該死的救護車
Get me a fucking ambulance!
你早知道的
You knew that would happen.
你對人類的行為一無所知
You know nothing of human behavior.
會有報復的
There will be retaliation.
你會受苦的
You will suffer.
受苦
Suffer?
我
Me?
你竟敢用這個詞
How dare you use such a word?
你對受苦一無所知
You know nothing of suffering.
我歡迎它熱情的擁抱
I welcome its warm embrace.
我的存在 就是為了分享它
I exist only to share its meaning.
罪惡和受苦是我的使命
Sin and suffering are my dominion.
是時候讓你學學了
Perhaps it's time you learned a little of the matters you seek to manage.
你在做什麼
What are you doing?
你知道我是誰嗎
Do you know who I am?
我不在乎
I care not.
諷刺
Irony.
你上正道了嗎
Are you the way?
放絕招吧
Do your worst!
你忘了我對"他"的第一個任務
You forget my first tasks for Him.[FK SUB]
我的命令已經被批准了
And my order has already been sanctioned.
看著我
Look at me.
你知道我
I'm all you know.
在痛苦和疼痛中鍛造
Forged in agony and pain.
我歡迎永恆的痛苦
I welcome the eternity of anguish.
那麼 釘子頭...
So, Pinhead....
現在結束今天的課程
Here endeth the lesson.
上帝哭了
Jesus wept!
可能不應這樣做
Probably should not have done that.
我無所畏懼
I have nothing to fear.
你忘了嗎
Did you forget?
她是放逐伊甸園那些人的天使
She is the angel who banished them from the Garden of Eden.
也許存在我們不能忍受的折磨
Perhaps there is a torture we cannot endure.
放逐
Banishment.
流亡
Exile.
回到凡人的世界
Back to the mortal world.
放逐
Banishment.
甜蜜的受苦
Sweet suffering.
The sweet suffering.
不
No!
FK SUB [養鬼吃人10：審判] 20180218
請繼續收看彩蛋
漢諾威市 德國
早上好
我們可入屋宣揚上帝的旨意嗎
二 連星期二都不是
Two, and it isn't even a Tuesday.